https://bazaarinegypt.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Glass Christmas ornaments online store Bazaar in EgyptYour privacy policy is important to us when you order
Glass Christmas ornaments online store Bazaar in Egypt privacy policy commitmentProtect your privacy, provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.We collect information:This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Bazaar in Egypt website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:NameAddressEmail addressPhone numberCredit/Debit Card Information ..(etc.)On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order an Egyptian gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:NameAddressPhone Number (etc.)The way we use information:We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalogue as well as updates on our new products and services, the information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our commitment to data security:To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Aiding us in this respect PayPal, as the exclusive, solely authorized retailer of goods and services provided by Bazaar in Egypt.Our commitment to children privacy:Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.How you can access or correct your information:You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.How to contact Bazaar in Egypt for all your glass Christmas ornaments needs
Should you have other questions, please send us an email at info@bazaarinegypt.com
Bazaar in Egypt Home Shop About us Wholesale Christmas Ornaments ContactsPrivacy PolicyGlass Ornaments BlogChristmas OrnamentsBlown Glass Christmas OrnamentsHomemade Christmas OrnamentsGlass Christmas BallsJoin Christmas Decorations Ideas
SIGN ME UP
+1 917 231 2089
info(at)bazaarinegypt.com
1182-21 150th Avenue Springfield Gardens, New YorkNY 11413, USA
Copyright 2020 © Bazaar in Egypt
